export const QUESTIONS = [
  {
    question: " Which one is JavaScript Data Types?",
    correctAnswer: "Boolean",
    wrongAnswers: ["Character", "Int", "Arr"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is === operator?",
    correctAnswer:
      " A strict equality operator, which returns true when the two operands have the same value without conversion.",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Checks only for equality in value",
      "A strict equality operator, which returns False",
      "None of them",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What would be the result of 3+2+”7″?",
    correctAnswer: "57",
    wrongAnswers: ["5+7", "75", "12"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which one is the anchor tag symbol?",
    correctAnswer: "<a></a>",
    wrongAnswers: ["<ul></ul>", "<p></p>", "<h3></h3>"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is DOM in JavaScript?",
    correctAnswer:
      "Programming interface that allows us to create, change, or remove elements from the document",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Helps to show HTML file ",
      "None of them",
      "Used for designing the web page",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function syntax?",
    correctAnswer: "function myFunction(p1, p2){return p1 * p2;}",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "func myFunction(p1, p2){return p1 * p2;} ",
      "Function (p1,p2){}",
      "function (p1, p2){return p1 * p2; ",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: " What is CSS?",
    correctAnswer:
      "Language for specifying how documents are presented to users",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "It is a Framework",
      "Basic building block of the Web",
      "All of them",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: " What is React?",
    correctAnswer: "JavaScript library for building user interfaces",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Can not be used to control parts of HTML pages",
      "TypeScript library for building user interfaces",
      "All of them",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What are all the looping structures in JavaScript?",
    correctAnswer: "for, while, do-while",
    wrongAnswers: ["let, var, const", "== ,(), +=", "int, num, true"],
  },
  {
    question: " Name a Git Commands and function?",
    correctAnswer: "Git Merge",
    wrongAnswers: ["npm Start", "Git On", "Git Clear"],
  },
];
